As far as features go,
应用功能差不多
the app is pretty much all done.
已经都创建完毕了
There is, however, one small change I want to make.
但是还需要进行一项小小的更改
If you push your app to the App Store,
如果要将应用发布到应用商店
there are some settings that you'll want to configure specifically for the
则需要专门针对应用商店配置一些设置
App Store,and that's what we can do inside of our app.json file.
我们将在 app.json 文件中进行配置
So what we can do is things like set the orientation.
我们可以设置 orientation
Say, we wanted only portrait mode to be active,
例如只希望设为 portrait 模式
meaning if you flip your phone,
表示如果翻转手机
nothing's really going to change. We can do that here.
什么也不会改变
We can also set the name of our application which we will call UdaciFitness.
还可以设置应用的 name 我们称之为 UdaciFitness
We can also put in a description here,
可以在这里添加 description
the best triathlon tracker ever.
“The best triathlon tracker ever”
Slug, which is something for Expo,
slug 专门针对 Expo 的设置
which basically is like your own custom URL.
就像自定义 URL
We'll say, udacifitness.
输入 udacifitness
Version, let's go ahead and give it a version 1.0.
将 version 设为 1.0
So I think it's pretty good.
不错
We can give it an icon,
可以设定一个 icon
which I'm just going to use as a local icon that's hosted on my site.
我将使用托管在我的网站上的本地图标
You can do the same.
你也可以这么做
So this way, when the user downloads the app,
这样的话 当用户下载该应用时
the icon they're going to see is this guy right here.
就会看到该图标
And then what we can do is we can also set up or edit our notification icon,
我们还可以设置或编辑通知图标
which I'm just going to have
我将使用相同的图片
the same image except it's going to be just a little bit smaller.
但是尺寸稍微小些
And when you do this,
这么设置时
you're not going to see a change on your emulators.
你不会在模拟器上看到变化
You need to actually build the app in order to see this notification change.
你需要实际地构建该应用 以便查看此通知变化
So if it doesn't work because you're not actually building the app.
如果不可行的话 则是因为你没有实际地构建应用
don't worry. Once you push it to the App Store, it should work.
别担心 当你发布到应用商店时 应该可行
And then the only other things we need in order to prep for
然后还需要为应用商店做准备的是
the App Store are these things right here, bundleIdentifier.
这些设置 包括 bundleIdentifier
What this is going to be is just an identifier for the App Store for your app.
它将是你的应用在应用商店上的标识符
So we'll just say udacifitness.exp,
设为 udacifitness.exp
and then Android also needs one as well.
Android 也需要设置一个
But in Android, it's called package and it's going to be the exact same name.
但是在 Android 中 称之为 package 名称完全一样
So that, after many videos, is basically it.
在看完这么多视频后 就差不多都搞定了
We learned how to build a React Native app. We learned about routing.
我们学习了如何构建 React Native 应用、导航功能
We learned about native e-stuff like notifications,
以及原生功能 例如通知
and we even learned about preparing our app for the App Store. Hope you enjoyed it.
甚至学习了如何为应用商店做准备。希望你能学的开心